<?xml version="1.0"?>
<FMECAs>

<FMECA>
<ID>F1</ID>
<Description>Insufficient voltage. Drone lands prematurely and is unable to return to base.</Description>
<Criticality>Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F2</ID>
<Description>Violation of minimum separation distance. Drone crashes into another drone.</Description>
<Criticality>Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F3</ID>
<Description>Inaccurate physical GPS. Physical drone fails to maintain accurate GPS positioning</Description>
<Criticality>Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F4</ID>
<Description>Inaccurate virtual GPS. Virtual drone simulator fails to maintain accurate GPS positioning</Description>
<Criticality>Non-Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F5</ID>
<Description>Incorrect diversion algorithm. Algorithm for guiding drones through congested airspace directs a drone into the path of another drone.</Description>
<Criticality>Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F6</ID>
<Description>Excessive drones in airspace. Algorithms not designed to maintain safety for so many drones.  Accidents result.</Description>
<Criticality>Medium Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F7</ID>
<Description>Physical component in drone fails during flight. Drone lands prematurely and/or crashes into other drones.</Description>
<Criticality>Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F8</ID>
<Description>Power indicator reports incorrect voltage. Drone fails to return to base and runs out of power.</Description>
<Criticality>Medium Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F9</ID>
<Description>Physical drones are orphaned when mode is changed to virtual. Physical drones are no longer under control.</Description>
<Criticality>Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F10</ID>
<Description>Communication failure between drone and central command. Physical drone fails to communicate critical status information</Description>
<Criticality>Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F11</ID>
<Description>Communication failure between central command and drone. Physical drone failes to receive message from ground control</Description>
<Criticality>Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F12</ID>
<Description>Drone position is outside of flight zone. One or more flight plan waypoints fall outside the flight zone</Description>
<Criticality>Medium Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F13</ID>
<Description>Drone lands on another drone. Landing sites are accidentally assigned the same coordinates and one drone lands on top of another one.</Description>
<Criticality>Medium </Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F15</ID>
<Description>Suicidal platoon leader. Platoon leader deliberately causes a crash into its own platoon</Description>
<Criticality>Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

<FMECA>
<ID>F16</ID>
<Description>Communication failure between drones in platoon. A tailing drone does not receive coordinates from its leader</Description>
<Criticality>Critical</Criticality>
</FMECA>

</FMECAs>
